Did October 7 shake your trust in the people of Gaza?
Yes of course.
I'm not in the left side of the political map of Israel,
I'm in the middle.
My wife was a member of the Knesset two years,
three years, ago four years ago.
we right in the middle of the political.
And we want to live in peace.
We want to live peacefully.
I told you there will be no peace in my generation,
but we want to live peacefully,
and I thought the things that we are doing,
the things that we are talking about them all the time,
would get into the mind of the majority of people in
in Gaza.
And when I saw all the pictures, that civilians,
not Nukhba, not the soldiers,
but the civilians coming to
kibbutzim and taking things from them...
and I heard from the soldiers,
that there are people (in Gaza) who are hiding
hostages and parts of bodies
in the in the refrigerator.
Of course it's disappointing.
Very disappointing.
I thought that we can talk.
Now I know that in this situation,
we can not talk. And I want to talk with them.
I want to live good here.
I don't care about them but I know that,
as I told you before,
if I want to live good here,
they have to live good over there.
And it's far away now.
It will take a long time after October 7th,
it will take much more time.